<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<document>

  <properties>
    <title>Home</title>
  </properties>

  <body>
    <section name="JMoney">
      <p>
	JMoney is a personal finance manager written in Java.
	It supports multiple accounts in different currencies, double entry banking, income/expense categories, various reports and Quicken file (QIF) exchange.
      </p>

      <p>
	Languages currently supported are English, German, Italian, Portuguese, Polish and Hungarian.
	If you want to translate JMoney into another language don't hesitate to contact us.
	JMoney is in development stage and may be buggy.
	If you find a bug please submit it to the <a href="http://sourceforge.net/tracker/?atid=117482&amp;group_id=17482&amp;func=browse">bug tracker</a>.
	There are many features planned: graphs, reconciling, online banking (HBCI), etc.
      </p>

      <p>
	<a href="http://jmoney.sf.net/webstart.php">
	  <center>
	    <img src="images/webstart.jpg" border="0"/>
	  </center>
	</a>
      </p>
    </section>

    <section name="News and status">
      <p>
      This section contains the latest news and current status regarding the JMoney project.
    </p>

      <subsection name="Current status">
	<p>
	  JMoney is now ready for use with Web Start (see above).
	  For Windows users, there is now a separate installer available.
	  Have a look at the <i>download</i> section.
	</p>
      </subsection>

      <subsection name="30 September 2003 - JMoney 0.4.4 released">
        <p>
	  Changes:
	</p>
	<ul>
	  <li>
	    Installer for Windows users
	  </li>
	  <li>
	    Java Web Start
	  </li>
	  <li>
	    MT940 import (patch by Jan-Pascal van Best)
	  </li>
	  <li>
	    Date of last entry will be used for date of new entries (patch py Andy Oliver).
	  </li>
	  <li>
	    Update to JasperReports 0.5.0
	  </li>
	</ul>
      </subsection>

      <subsection name="23 January 2003 - JMoney 0.4.3 released">
        <p>
	  Changes:
	</p>
	<ul>
	  <li>
	    Localization to Hungarian (thanks to Agoston Deim)
	  </li>
	  <li>
	    Update to JasperReports 0.4.5
	  </li>
	  <li>
	    New entries are initialized with the current date.
	  </li>
	  <li>
	    Deletion of entries, accounts and categories must be confirmed.
	  </li>
	</ul>
      </subsection>

      <subsection name="19 December 2002 - JMoney 0.4.2 released">
	<p>
	  This release supports Polish (thanks to Maciej Dziergwa) and has some minor bug fixes.
	</p>
      </subsection>

      <subsection name="27 October 2002 - JMoney 0.4.1 released">
	<p>
	  On Windows systems reports didn't display correctly.
	  There were only three lines on the report and nothing more.
	  This release fixes this problem.
	</p>
      </subsection>

      <subsection name="18 October 2002 - JMoney 0.4.0 released">
	<p>
	  This is the first version of JMoney that provides reports.
	  Two statistics are available: account balances and income/expense.
	  The reports are fully customizable and can be printed.
	  Reports are generated using the <a href="http://jasperreports.sourceforge.net">JasperReports</a> report generation tool.
	</p>
	<p>
	  Other Changes:
	</p>
	<ul>
	  <li>
	    Wait dialog:
            Since it takes it's time to open and save a JMoney file a wait dialog is shown during this time.
	  </li>
	  <li>
	    Portuguese translation:
	    Another translation could be added thanks to Max Gomes.
	  </li>
	</ul>
      </subsection>

      <subsection name="29 September 2002 - JMoney 0.3.3 released">
	<p>
	  Changes in this version include:
	</p>
	<ul>
	  <li>
	    Entry filter:
	    Entries in an account can be filtered with a search string.
	    The filter either searches all fields of an entry or a specified field.
	  </li>
	  <li>
	    Auto completion for new entries:
	    While you edit the description field of a new entry, JMoney tries to complete it by searching older entries and suggesting one that might match.
	  </li>
	  <li>
	    Tool bar:
	    JMoney now features a tool bar with the most important buttons. However, some aren't implemented yet.
	  </li>
	  <li>
	    Icons in menu:
	    Some Menu entries are now enhanced by icons.
	  </li>
	  <li>
	    Bugfixes: QIF export and display of changed categories.
	  </li>
	</ul>
      </subsection>

      <subsection name="27 September 2002 - Website redesign">
	<p>
	  You probably have noticed that JMoney has a new website!
	</p>
	<p>
	  This website is generated with <a href="http://jakarta.apache.org/turbine/maven/">Maven</a>.
	  Maven is a really great tool.
	  If you are a programmer and not a website designer then you'll love it.
	  But Maven is not restricted to the generation of websites; it is a Java project management and project comprehension tool.
	  Just visit their website.
	</p>
      </subsection>

      <subsection name="12 September 2002 - JMoney 0.3.2 released">
	<p>
	  This version contains various changes:
	</p>
	<ul>
	  <li>
	    Simple/extended view of entries:
	    You can choose between two different views for entries.
	    The simple view shows the whole entry on one line, although not all fields are displayed.
	    The extended view shows all entries of a field on three lines instead of one.
	  </li>
	  <li>
	    Sortable Entries:
	    Entries are sortable by their fields.
	    Just click on the labels (e.g. Date, Description, etc) in the entry view.
	  </li>
	  <li>
	    Ant build support:
	    Now, JMoney can be built with Ant.
	  </li>
	  <li>
	    Minor bugfixes.
	  </li>
	</ul>
      </subsection>

      <p>
	<script language="JavaScript" src="http://m1.nedstatbasic.net/basic.js">
	</script>
	<script language="JavaScript">
	  <!--
          nedstatbasic("ABzXIwZmkRUZZjSCUOz4fSXbrZWg", 0);
	  // -->
	</script>
	<noscript>
	  <a href="http://v1.nedstatbasic.net/stats?ABzXIwZmkRUZZjSCUOz4fSXbrZWg">
	    <img src="http://m1.nedstatbasic.net/n?id=ABzXIwZmkRUZZjSCUOz4fSXbrZWg"
		 border="0" width="18" height="18"/>
	  </a>
	</noscript>
      </p>

    </section>
  </body>

</document>
